we've grown email list to over hundreds
of thousands of people and sent emails
that have scaled businesses to tens of
millions of dollars online but what if
you send an email to your list and
nobody responds and what's the
difference between what actually gets
people to respond to your emails and
actually do what you ask and ones that
flounder in this video I want to walk
you through the process of how we create
the best emails that get opened and the
process that you can use in your
business to make sure that you get more
clients and nurture and engage with them
more again for those of you I haven't
met yet my name is Jeremiah Kowski I
built and scaled multiple coaching
businesses to the 20 million doll a year
Co Mark and I want to show you exactly
what to do with your email marketing I
want you to imagine this that you send
an email to your list you got maybe
10,000 people on the list and nobody
opens
it nobody reads it nobody clicks it uh
that sounds like a horror story no we
don't want to talk about that right now
what if on the flip side of that you
sent an email out and 50 to 60% of the
people that you sent it to open the
email about 20% of them clicked the link
and you can even see in the statistics
the people came back again and again and
again and read the email well that
second story is what it's like when we
send out our emails and there's a
process to doing this that I go through
that I want to teach you in this video
how to come up with the best things to
say in your your emails how to never
struggle wondering what to do and how to
actually connect with your prospects the
most when you are building a coaching
business there are people that are out
there that we connect with we want to
get them on our email list I have a lot
of great training all about growing your
email list on this channel and that's
what I coach my clients on in my
accelerator program as I come alongside
them to grow their email list to get
more clients every single week in their
business but what I want to talk about
is that once you grow your email list
how do you actually turn that into cash
flow how do you actually turn that into
six or even seven figures for you
because just having an email list isn't
enough but if you can actually
strategically know what to send to your
list you can get people buying from you
and coming back and reading and opening
every email mitigating unsubscribes and
making sure that you're sending the
right things to people instead of boring
them the whole time and that's what
happens whenever we send out our emails
is that we have people that open again
and again and again all the different
emails that we send out a lot of people
in marketers say email marketing is dead
and you should be doing all these other
strategies but I'll tell you this that
it is the most successful thing that you
can do is to grow your email list now
there's a process that I Mentor people
on when it comes to Growing their email
list and getting people to actually read
those emails is a process that you can
learn to actually know exactly what to
say in your emails one of the best
things that we can do is we can look at
what is out there in the marketplace
already who is sending emails in the
marketplace and the best way to do this
is that if you go to your social media
whether it be Facebook whether it be
Instagram whether it be Twitter you can
find advertising campaigns from people
here's one right here we can click on an
advertising campaign from somebody and
read about it and nine times out of 10
what you're going to notice is that
there's some way to put in your name and
email address onto a page on an
advertisement again I I I don't even
know what this offer is is I literally
clicked it I guess you can send pictures
of your dog to them as well that's kind
of cute but either way here's another
idea right here here's another offer
okay this is going to send you a free
pdf if you just give your name and email
address all right so what I like to do
is this is that I will actually go
through and I'll click on different
offers across these different platforms
whether it be on x.com whether it be on
Instagram and I'll see who is
advertising who is marketing
and I'll actually click on certain
sponsored ads or sponsored posts and I
will literally sign up with my email
address onto these for this one
reason it's not that I'm going to become
a client to these businesses and and and
I'm a firm believer by the way in the
law of reaping and sewing do under
others what you would have them do under
you but I know for a fact that people do
this even in our offers because this is
the way that it goes and this is the
best practice that you can do to get
really really good ideas for emails is
to sign up two different offers and to
have an email address specifically that
you can use to be able to have people
send and email those to you and so
here's what I have is I have an
inbox that is literally flooded full
of
emails from people that I've signed up
with like every day just hundreds
of emails that I'm receiving from
marketers competitors even of my own
business and so what I do is actually
scroll through here and I can see and
find okay what's a good email that I
might use to send my list and so if I'm
looking for an idea I can even type in
topics on this account you can see over
59,000 emails that I've received from
multiple marketers so let's say I'm
marketing something about Facebook ads
right here okay okay I can now see every
email that somebody sent out about
marketing Facebook ads let's say we say
organic content we can type that in okay
let's say I do ever Evergreen let's see
who's sending an email out with the word
Evergreen Evergreen launching okay
here's one right here Q&A on Evergreen
Evergreen sales is a Hot Topic the idea
is somebody's trying to get you to go
here to the class emails that sell email
launch this course it's a class $99 and
so the idea is is that if you sign up to
a number of even your competitors's
emails you're able to see exactly what
they are sending and that gives you
ideas now here's the next step right
here that's really exciting is that I
can actually go in and I can take an
email from somebody this is just a
random email that I pulled up and I can
pull this into Ai and I can tell AI this
I can
say take the following email and rewrite
it to promote my free
training all
about getting more coaching clients with
Facebook ads and knowing
exactly who to Target act as an expert
in this and rewrite the email below for
that topic to
persuade people to register okay so then
I'm going to actually paste the email
that I copied right
here I'm going to paste it in here and
the AI is going to rewrite it for my
offer are you ready to const
consistently attract more coaching
clients using Facebook ads without
confusion of who to Target in this free
training I'll reveal exactly what's
working right now when it comes to
getting more clients how to run ads that
convert how to identify your target
audience just reply yes to this email
and I'll send you all the details or
instead of that we could include a link
to it whether you're brand new to ad are
already running a campaign this training
will give you clear proven steps so
right here I could take this email and I
could schedule this to then send people
to my training all about Facebook ads by
the way you can find the training in the
description below it's right there now
here's another thing that I have that's
a great way to come up with ideas for an
email but what if what if I want to send
a piece of content to somebody and I
want to make sure that they click it or
they or they consume it well here's
another process that I like to take any
video that you post onto YouTube
gets transcribed and what I love to do
is I love to send my audience my YouTube
videos maybe you're watching this
YouTube video because you're on my email
list and I sent it to you and I sent you
a notification if not again make sure to
subscribe below go grab the free
training and then I will send you emails
anytime that I put up a new video or
training that's worth it for you to
check out okay what I want to show you
is this this is a video that I just did
this past week called creating an
irresistible offer that sells out your
coaching program up and I have another
video right here that I just posted best
AI apps to get more coaching clients
without losing your authenticity this is
probably one of the coolest videos I've
actually posted recently and if I click
on show transcript I can actually see
that there's a transcript of the video
that YouTube gives me now here's the fun
part about this under show
transcript if I press toggle timestamps
I can copy the transcript the whole
thing right here and I can tell chat GPT
I can say this
watch take the following transcript and
write an email to my email list of
people who are the Target demographic of
the transcript
below write a persuasive email that will
get them
to open it read it make it engaging and
high dopamine
triggering why not makes it makes it
good for that and
then have the call to action to be to
check out the
YouTube
video below is the transcript okay so
then I'll paste the whole transcript
from my YouTube video on here and we'll
have the AI go to work to actually
create an email to get people on this
how to 2x or 3x your coaching business
with a without losing your voice what if
you could double or triple your impact
in your coaching business while staying
true to your voice sounds to could be
true it's not here's the thing AI isn't
new most people don't know how to use it
the right way my latest video I break
down how to help you get how we help our
clients leverage AI to scale their
businesses to new heights without
sounding like robots or losing their
authentic Personal Touch the AI tools
that we use that you can Master how to
create personalized video audio and
written content exact strategies my
clients are using six figures and Beyond
why your competitors are already using
AI don't miss this check out the video
now and learn how to use it to grow your
business I've helped coaches and course
creators this is awesome this is
actually a great email right here that
we could send out and I actually even
like it added founder of the client
growth accelerator that's so cool
awesome so if I copy this and in fact
I'm going to send this email out to my
list that's another great idea now
here's another thing that you could do
just to improve it just just for another
layer on top of it act as an expert in
email marketing to warm marketing off
audience for coaches and mentors and an
expert at direct
response
copyrighting assess the
email the email above then write an
improved version based on your
recommendations okay so what it's going
to do is it's going to read the email
and the AI is literally going to assess
it make it even better and improve
it by writing it this way boost your
coaching is with AI the secret your
competitors don't want you to know have
you ever wondered how you can double
even triple here's the truth AI is
Ultimate Game Changer but here's the
thing most people don't know how to use
it in this free video I break down
multiply your impact without sacrificing
your authenticity use AI to create
personalized content that sounds just
like you and get access to the top AI
tools that's actually much better how
that's written and so whenever I'm
sending an email out that's one of the
things that I will do if I have a piece
of content that I want people to consume
or I want to send that to them what I'm
going to do is I'm actually going to use
AI to craft an email to send out to them
now here's the thing how do you know
what content people actually want to see
or consume from you in your email
because that's the other part of it
let's say you don't know what content to
create okay AI is really cool at coming
up with ideas for this based on whatever
it is that you're doing so let's just
say this um I I want to reverse engineer
this and ask AI make me
a psychographic and
demographic client Avatar profile of the
person this is written to okay it's
going again it's going to take my
transcript and do this by the way you
could take somebody else's transcript or
a competitor of yours to be able to do
this in there and this is actually
extremely accurate to who we reach uh
primarily female yep that's very true 30
to 50 years old coaches mentors
Consultants course creators in niches
like Health Wellness
that's perfect that's amazing okay so
this is this is pulling up exactly what
it is that our clients care about the
ones that that have worked with us and
so now what I'm going to do is this is
I'm going to take
this this Avatar right here and I'm
going to have the AI reverse engineer
this into some ideas for Content that we
can send out in our emails here's the
truth is that most people they don't
want to just
look at content that sounds like what
everybody else creates they want it to
be tailor made for them and the best way
that you can come up with that content
is it's twofold number one you can use
AI to simulate this okay take the
following Avatar actually I'm going to
make a new chat for
this take the following Avatar and
generate me 50 YouTube video ideas that
are unique and
very different from each other by the
way typos don't matter when it comes to
AI just keep typing it's much better
that way based on the
following
Avatar okay so it's going to read that
Avatar and it's going to come up with 50
unique videos or pieces of content for
that type of person that I want to work
with how to scale your coaching business
without losing Personal Touch Ultimate
Guide to automated systems in your
business how to set boundaries and
create perfect work like balance as a
coach top five marketing mistakes to
avoid client acquisition how to attract
high quality clients behind the scenes
how I manage my business with a small
team balancing coaching and content this
is amazing honestly what this is giving
me is incredible ideas very specifically
as to what I know my audience would want
and I can reverse engineer any of these
into videos in fact this one's really
good right here how to build stronger
relationships with your clients at
scale can you generate me an outline for
a YouTube video based on this how to
build stronger relationships with your
clients at SK scale techniques for
maintaining deep relationships act as an
expert in this and so what this is able
to do is it's able to generate us an
outline for a YouTube video on this
topic right here it's able to give us
ideas of how to start it do you feel
like growing your business means losing
your personal touch as coaches scale
maintaining meaningful relationships is
important and then it gives you ideas of
what to do for the first 6 minutes in
the video as well off of this the first
6 minutes is one of the most important
parts of keeping people engaged in our
content
from here what I can do is I can
actually go ask it to write an email to
persuade somebody to watch this video
and I and I actually paused the video
and actually typed all this in that's
why I'm not typing it in because I just
want to show you this really quickly as
to how this is done so what it was able
to do is it was able to write an email
on how to persuade somebody to watch
this video and and this is an email that
we wanted that we could send to our list
off of this I know how important it is
for you to grow your business that's why
I made this video okay so that's not as
strong as we would like it and
unfortunately this is how a lot of
people use AI is they're not creating
strong enough emails this way so that's
why we go back and we ask it again based
on the above what's written above act as
an expert at direct response email
marketing and assess it's I guess it
says asses but
assess and rewrite the email above to
make it more persuasive to get people to
watch the Youtube video sure here's a
revised version written in the direct
response marketing design to be more
persuasive if you're serious about
growing your coaching Business Without
sacrificing your personal relationships
you work so hard to build it you need to
watch this in just a few minutes my
latest video reviews how to to scale
your coaching practice while still
keeping your personal touch I'm going to
give you simple automation strategies
how deepen client relationship
Improvement tactics to build a loyal
community so the idea behind this is
that what we're able to do is we're able
to come up with strategically what we
want to say to actually get people to
engage with our video we got ideas for
what we're going to talk about in the
video and when you use content this is
how you're able to nurture that trust
and relationship with your clients when
it comes to building your business the
number one way to get clients is to give
people what they want more of and any of
us no matter what business we're in
there are people that are out there that
need what we know and understand if you
can take your knowledge and expertise
you can turn it into a business in a
course or coaching program and the way
that we get those clients is we show
people how to be able to take their
knowledge and expertise and be able to
turn that into something that they can
sell online and so what you can do no
matter what you're doing no matter what
topic you work with people on you can
create content that delivers value to
people and then use that as a way to P
pull people over and draw them into the
programs that you are selling now again
one of the best ways to do this is they
have some way that people can actually
just sign up to your email list instead
of just straight selling people you
might notice in this video I'm not
selling you anything but I'm sharing
value with you and we have different
offers I got a free training all about
Facebook ads you can get on the waiting
list for my coaching program that we
work with our clients every single week
to help them develop their marketing
strategies their advertising campaigns
their landing pages to close more sales
and to ultimately make the kind of money
that they want to make in their business
but I don't just come out there and I'm
not just like hey you need to buy this
that's the problem that most people do
in their business is that they're trying
to just say hey you should buy this and
nobody's going to buy from you if you do
that so what you have to do is you have
to learn how to figure out what people
actually desire what is the desire that
they have and dig deeper about two or
three layers so for instance if somebody
says I want to get more clients in my
coaching business in fact we can even
use AI to simulate this if if I work
with a coach who wants to get more
clients in their business dig three
layers deep as to
what issues and skills they need to
learn that I could teach them in a
course
okay to coach you want to address skills
and strategies on how to convert
retain and attract convert and retain so
lack of client acquisition strategy
limited online presence and branding
inconsistent marketing effort sales
hesitation so when somebody tells me
that they want to get more clients I
want to go deeper into the layers beyond
the surface level of that layer number
two they don't know what their Niche is
they don't know how to position
themselves they don't know how to
generate leads they don't know their
messaging they don't know how to create
the right content layer number three
they don't know the business model they
don't understand the client Journey they
don't understand how to be a thought
leader how to enroll people in sales
what's the right content strategy their
email marketing and so this is what I'll
do is I will actually create content
around the third layer and then as I'm
creating that third layer of content I
figure out what are the topics that my
clients that want to work with me really
want to learn from me and that's what I
deliver and I send those to my email
list now I'm not just sending content to
people though because I'm making sure
that any time that I send content that
if somebody consumes that content they
know about what I have to offer like
I've already mentioned to you I have a
coaching program where I work with
people and I come alongside them as a
part of their success strategy to get
more clients in their business I become
a part of their team to be able to get
them more sales more leads more clients
and I've worked with thousands of people
over the years to be able to do this in
their business and I'd love to work with
you as well Bing see so I just mentioned
what I have for sale how I sell it to
people you know what it is but I'm not
here just straight pitching you right
here I'm actually just using it as an
example but it was just if not more
effective than if I made this a sales
pitch if this whole video was just a
sales pitch you wouldn't watch it but
I'm able to talk about what I do with
people how I help them with their
messaging with their branding with their
Niche and all of that and maybe you're
like well jerem now you're pitching me
I'm not I'm giving you an example of how
to do this in your own business now I
would love to work with you in my
program I think it would be incredible
to have you a part of that and you can
get on the waiting list to jump in you
can go watch the free training that I
have all about Facebook ads where I walk
you through how we're using Facebook ads
to get more clients when you can learn
to dig deeper two or three layers deep
into what somebody wants to learn in
fact you can even go deeper you can go
can you go four more layers deeper from
this with more ideas okay and this is
giving us ideas for what you could
create a program or course or training
about uh Niche branding lead gen but I
want to see if I can go four more layers
client experience and transformation
delivering exceptional client results
this is what I talk about in my coaching
program deep marketing and funnel
psychology understanding the buyer
psychology conversion rate optimization
again we got courses in our program all
about this how to do all of this type of
stuff content marketing that works
Advanced sales system systems how do you
build a sales team scaling High ticket
sales that's for advanced level people
the art of upselling and cross selling
refining pricing models Automation and
delegation and time management
automating lead nurture and followup
Outsourcing and delegation so people
don't burn themselves out again inside
of my coaching program those are part of
what we teach we got full courses full
community of people that we work with to
show you how to build an audience how to
build community and how to get more
clients for you
but what's really cool is we were able
to use Ai and I didn't even give any of
the AI any ideas about this and it
literally knows exactly how I help my
clients and no matter what Niche you're
in no matter what topic you coach on no
matter what business model you're in you
can simulate this now the best thing to
do is then to take and go out there and
go find some clients that you can work
with go find people that want to work
with you that want to be your clients
that want to come inside of your e
ecosystem to to see what you have going
on and listen to them pay attention to
the questions that they are asking you
pay attention to the problems that they
have pay attention to the solutions that
they are looking for and when you do
this you can take somebody and turn them
into a paid client by connecting with
them online total stranger building
trust with them you build no like and
trust and then leading them over to a
paid program that you have now again as
I mentioned my coaching program the
client growth accelerator it's 200 bucks
a month right now at the time of this
recording and I work with people every
single month every single week inside of
there every single day we're in the
Facebook group on their ads on their
copyrighting on their messaging on
finding exactly the ways to get more
clients so they have consistent profits
in their business so that they have
consistent clients coming in so they
have consistent cash flow coming in so
that that creates consistent Financial
Freedom I know I said the word
consistent like five times because
that's the motto of what we do is
consistency so that you're not
struggling or wondering you're burnt out
where are my next where's my next
paycheck going to come from where's my
where my clients going to come from so
that you know exactly what to do to get
people to come into your business and so
listen again if you'd love to work with
me click the link below jump on our
waiting list join us for one of our free
trainings and make sure to stay
subscribed to this Channel and they'll
talk soon have a good one